{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the Batman comics, by what other name is the villain Dr. Jonathan Crane known?","correct_answer":"Scarecrow","incorrect_answers":["Bane","Calendar Man","Clayface"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In what Homestuck Update was [S] Game Over released?","correct_answer":"October 25th, 2014","incorrect_answers":["April 13th, 2009","April 8th, 2012","August 28th, 2003"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the Homestuck Series, what is the alternate name for the Kingdom of Lights?","correct_answer":"Prospit","incorrect_answers":["No Name","Golden City","Yellow Moon"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What year was the first San Diego Comic-Con?","correct_answer":"1970","incorrect_answers":["2000","1990","1985"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"When was the Garfield comic first published?","correct_answer":"1978","incorrect_answers":["1982","1973","1988"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What is the real hair colour of the mainstream comic book version (Earth-616) of Daredevil?","correct_answer":"Blonde","incorrect_answers":["Auburn","Brown","Black"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In what year did the first &quot;The Walking Dead&quot; comic come out?","correct_answer":"2003","incorrect_answers":["2001","2006","1999"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the &quot;Archie&quot; comics, who was Jughead&#039;s first girlfriend?","correct_answer":"Joani","incorrect_answers":["Ethel","Debbi","Margret"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the webcomic &quot;Ava&#039;s Demon&quot;, what sin is &quot;Nevy Nervine&quot; based off of? ","correct_answer":"Envy ","incorrect_answers":["Sloth","Wrath ","Lust"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"When Batman trolls the online chat rooms, what alias does he use?","correct_answer":"JonDoe297","incorrect_answers":["iAmBatman","BWayne13","BW1129"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In 1978, Superman teamed up with what celebrity, to defeat an alien invasion?","correct_answer":"Muhammad Ali","incorrect_answers":["Mike Tyson","Sylvester Stallone","Arnold Schwarzenegger"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which of the following rings from the DC Comics&#039; &quot;Lantern Corps&quot; are classified as Parasitic?","correct_answer":"Indigo (Compassion)","incorrect_answers":["Green (Willpower)","White (Life)","Yellow (Fear)"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What are the names of the two &quot;Canon fan trolls&quot; in &quot;Homestuck&quot;?","correct_answer":"Mierfa Durgas and Nektan Whelan","incorrect_answers":["The Wrycrown and Voksea Olkido","Aikter Frekik and Xagrai Ollomu","Grekei Ceknux and Riya Camacho"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Better known by his nickname Logan, what is Wolverine&#039;s birth name?","correct_answer":"James Howlett","incorrect_answers":["Logan Wolf","Thomas Wilde","John Savage"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What are the Three Virtues of Bionicle?","correct_answer":"Unity, Duty, Destiny","incorrect_answers":["Build, Play, Change","Work, Play, Live","Forge, Build, Fight"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the Hellboy universe, what was Abe Sapien&#039;s birth name?","correct_answer":"Langdon Everett Caul","incorrect_answers":["Lord Baltimore","Sir Edward Grey","Landis Pope"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which pulp hero made appearances in Hellboy and BPRD comics before getting his own spin-off?","correct_answer":"Lobster Johnson","incorrect_answers":["Roger the Homunculus","The Spider","The Wendigo"]}]}